https://www.4legsphysio.co.uk/privacy/

CALL SUSIE: 07815 821160
MENU:
PRIVACY POLICY
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you use our contact form to get in touch with us.
How will we use the information about you?
We will use the information provided to contact you if your enquiry requires a reply. We will not share your information with anyone else, apart from veterinary surgeons if necessary during treatment, unless required to do so by law.
Access to your information and corrections
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us. Photographic ID will be required before your request can be fulfilled. We will provide the information within 30 days in PDF format.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This website uses Google Analytics which tracks visitor behaviour via cookies and compiles statistical reports on website activity.
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org
You can set your web browser to not accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies.
Other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites, you should read their own privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page.
Email Susie or call her on 07815 821160 to talk through your options today
© 2020 4 Legs Physio
Privacy •
Sitemap
website by dunmoweb
